// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Prudential Reason of Power Sharing stresses more on?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Reducing the possibility of conflict between various social groups",
      "A fair chance to minority",
      "Bringing stability in the political order",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Identify the distinguishing feature of the Federal system?",
    answer: "Government power is divided between different levels of government.",
    options: [
      "Power is distributed among the legislature, executive and judiciary",
      "Elected officials exercise supreme power in the government",
      "The national government gives some power to the provincial government",
      "Government power is divided between different levels of government"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Government power is divided between different levels of government?",
    answer: "USA.",
    options: [
      "India",
      "USA",
      "Spain",
      "Belgium"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the given statement about the India constitution is wrong?",
    answer: "Gives official status to one religion.",
    options: [
      "Gives official status to one religion.",
      "Ensures equality of citizens within religious minorities",
      "Gives official status of one religion",
      "Prohibits discrimination on the grounds of religion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is the oldest political party of India ?",
    answer: "Indian National Congress",
    options: [
      "The Communist Party",
      "Indian National Congress",
      "Bhartiya Janta Party",
      "Bahujan Samaj Party"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which party rules in China ?",
    answer: "Communist Party",
    options: [
      "Communist Party",
      "Socialist Party",
      "Maoist Party",
      "Liberal Party"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who allots symbol to political parties?",
    answer: "The Election Commission",
    options: [
      "The Party leaders",
      "The Election Commission",
      "The Government of India",
      "The constitution of India"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The number of registered political parties with the Election Commission of India is",
    answer: "750 parties",
    options: [
      "More than 750 parties",
      "Less than 750 parties",
      "705 parties",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Among the options, which country has the highest participation of woman in public life?",
    answer: "Sweden and Africa",
    options: [
      "Norway and Sri Lanka",
      "Sweden and India",
      "Nepal and Finland",
      "Sweden and Africa"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Select the correct option for the definition, 'A woman or man who believes in equal rights and opportunities for men and women'",
    answer: "Feminist",
    options: [
      "Social Change",
      "Caste Hierarchy",
      "Patriarchy",
      "Feminist"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];